qqt38.com 2019-05-06

# Privacy Policy - TwitchFollowers

### Privacy Policy of twitchfollowers.com

Surely the privacy to be important for us to protect. As our efforts in protecting your privacy, we will offer an explanation of the information practices on the internet and you have the option to describe how you in accumulating information and how you would use it. In our efforts to make this page easier to find, we place this page on the home page website which allows a wide range of personal information will be requested for special purposes with your consent in full. For example your name, address, email, phone number. The action we are asking for your personal data we do not mean to criminals, but only if you do want to take advantage of our features to its full potential.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfilment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
  * We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

 **Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Vendors who use cookies to serve ads on this website is Google. Google as a third party ad vendors allowing them in the granting of ads to site visitors of Trends Fashion Daily that come back again to the visitors who had promised to this website and other websites. And keep in mind that we do not associate the cookies or anonymous identifier by category relating to race, sexual orientation, politics, and religion. We also will not combine personal information with DoubleClick’s Cookie information, unless we obtain the consent of you.

 **Collection of Personal Information**

When you visit the site of Home Design Ideas this internet IP address used will be stored and reused as you will access the site by logging combined with time, as well as of press time for accessing this site. Details like this technique eventually used to be pure to analyze trends, release website, monitor the movement of visitors to the site as well as a very extensive market information for personal use. But again I emphasize, that the most important is the IP address that is recorded will not be dealt with personally identifiable information.

 **Information Security**

We work hard to protect you and other visitors from unauthorized access or alteration, destruction, or unauthorized disclosure of the information we hold.

 **Changes to this Privacy Statement**

Some contents of this statement could have been us change it at any time to change to a better direction without informing you if there will be changes before. When there are things to do about Home Design Ideas site, it may be a privacy policy or perhaps other questions do not hesitate to Contact Us.
